universalbox.com 2013-11-22

# UniversalBox > Privacy policy

Protecting the individual's privacy on the Internet is crucial to the future of Internet-based business and the move toward a true Internet economy. UniversalBox has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to secure and trustworthy Internet commerce and the individual's right to privacy.

**Consent.** By using this Website, you consent to the collection and use of the information as described here. If we decide to make changes to this privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you will always know what information we collect, and how we use it.

**Use and Purpose of Collected Personal Data.** On our Websites, we only store personal information relating to you with your permission. You may choose to reveal information to us if, for example, you register or complete a survey. Companies in the UniversalBox may use the information internationally in connection with processing your inquiries and orders or to help improve our products and services. We would only share such information with third parties outside the UniversalBox with your express permission or as required by the applicable law. Information is used solely for the purposes described below.

**Privacy across the Entire UniversalBox Network.** Any information that you submit to out site will not be forward or give to third person. We safeguard your privacy interests around the world by ensuring that this UniversalBox site adheres to our international data-protection principles described in this statement. We bind our employees to observe your privacy and confidentiality rights.

**Details.**

  * What Information Do We Collect and Why? 
    * IP Addresses 
      * We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems, to administer our Website, and to gather demographic information. When you visit our site, we recognize only your domain name and not your e-mail address. We will see your e-mail address only if you give it to us by filling out a form or by sending us an e-mail message.

**Cookies.** We use cookies to deliver personalized content, to save you having to re-enter your password repeatedly, and to tailor our information offerings to how you and others use the site.

**User Registration.** If you choose to register, we can send you requested information or products, other product information, news, or promotions.

**E-mail Addresses.** If you choose to give us your e-mail address, we will communicate with you via e-mail. We do not share your e-mail address with others outside the UniversalBox of companies. You can choose not to receive any more e-mail at any time. Depending on how your e-mail application is set up, information about you may be transmitted automatically when you send e-mail to UniversalBox. If you choose to register for third-party services, we may need to send some information from your universalbox.com registration to the service provider, possibly including your e-mail address — but only if your requested service cannot be provided otherwise.

**Online Surveys.** Our surveys may ask you for demographic information, such as postal codes or your industry sector. If the online survey collects contact data, we may use that data to send you further information only if we specifically asked for your permission in the survey. You are free to retract any permission you gave.

**Links to Other Sites.** This site contains links to other sites. UniversalBox is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Websites.

**Choice/Opt-Out.** You can opt out of receiving e-mail communications from us whenever you like. You only need to e-mail us to have your name and details removed from UniversalBox's e-mail list or registration database.

**Inquiries.** If you have any questions about this privacy statement or if you wish to view or update the information we have about you, feel free to contact support@universalbox.com.
